// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many computer languages are in use?",
    answer: "2000",
    options: [
      "20",
      "50",
      "5000",
      "2000"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who founded Apple Computer?",
    answer: "Steve Jobs",
    options: [
      "Stephen Hawking",
      "Steve Jobs",
      "Bill Gates",
      "Stephen Fry"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
    answer: "Motherboard",
    options: [
      "Monitor",
      "Keyboard",
      "Motherboard",
      "Mouse"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not one of the early “protocols,” or ways to use the Internet?",
    answer: "Blogging",
    options: [
      "Telnet",
      "Gopher",
      "FTP",
      "Blogging"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?",
    answer: "World Wide Web",
    options: [
      " Western Washington World",
      "Worldwide Weather",
      "Wide Width Wickets",
      "World Wide Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these products is not made by the Apple Corporation?",
    answer: "IMAX",
    options: [
      "iPod",
      "iMac",
      "iPhone",
      "IMAX"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the name for a computer pointing device?",
    answer: "A Mouse",
    options: [
      "Ram",
      "Monitor",
      "Sound Card",
      "A Mouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When did the compact disc first appear on the market?",
    answer: "1982",
    options: [
      "1989",
      "1955",
      "1992",
      "1982"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "To which of these devices is the cellular telephone most closely related?",
    answer: "Radio",
    options: [
      "Telescope",
      "Light bulb",
      "Telegraph",
      "Radio"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " What does fiber optic cable resemble, in terms of size?",
    answer: "human hair",
    options: [
      "Telephone wire",
      "Bamboo",
      "Pipeline",
      "human hair"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];